bharatplaza.in 2013-07-28

# Privacy Policy at Bharat Plaza

We respect your privacy and are committed to maintaining it. When you shop on our Web store, we will ask you to input your information and will collect Personal Information from you such as your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, telephone/ mobile number, product selections, credit card or other payment information and password.

We may also collect information about where you are on the internet (eg the URL you came from, IP address, domain types like .com .au and .com), your browser type, where you located in the country, the pages of our website that were viewed during your visit, the advertisements you clicked on. We may collect this information even if you do not register with us. None of this data is of a personal nature and will help us improve the quality of our service.

We at Bharatplaza Online Marketing Team recognize your right to confidentiality and are committed to protecting your privacy. We do not furnish any identifiable information at the individual level regarding its customers to any third party. The information you give to us is held with the utmost care and security. This information is collected primarily to ensure that we are able to fulfill your requirements and to deliver you a truly personalized shopping experience. When navigating our web site, personal information about you is not collected automatically or without your knowledge.

We are also bound to cooperate fully should a situation arise where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a customer. We may share non-personal, non-individual statistical or demographic information in aggregate form with our marketing partners, advertisers or other third-parties for research and advertising purposes. In other words, we will not tell our marketing partners that you purchased a specific product, but we may tell them how many customers purchased that product.

## Security of Information

When you place an order on bharatplaza.in website for a product, we offer the use of a secure server. The Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encrypts all the information you input before it is sent to us. This prevents your personal data from being interpreted even if hacked while submitting it to our server. At the time of submitting your Credit Card details you will be redirected to a Highly Secure Payment server where BHARATPLAZA its associates have no access to your information. BHARATPLAZA always see to that your privacy is maintained at all time during your time of shopping at our Web Store. We will not disclose any sort of personally identifiable information except when you give us requisite permission or under special circumstances such as when the law requires it.

A cookie is a piece of information that is stored on your computer's hard drive by your web browser which tracks your movements within websites. Our site uses cookies to keep track of how often you visit our site, the contents of your shopping cart, previous purchases and to deliver content specific to your interests. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies but usually you can alter the settings of your browser to prevent automatic acceptance.

In case if you feel that your personal information should be change then you can change those information by "SIGN IN" and update the profile. There, you will be allowed to change any of your personal information that you might have entered before with us. In case you have trouble changing your information, you may email us via TICKET, our customer care department will help you to do so.

In summary BHARATPLAZA always respect the privacy of our customers completely. We use the information we collect on the Store to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

## About BharatPlaza...

Bharatplaza, Jodhpur, Rajasthan (India) is a leading Manufacturers, Exporters and Suppliers Designer Sarees, Bridal Saris, Jodhpuri Mens Ethnic Wear, Embroidered Sarees, Indian Menswear Manufacturers, Wedding Sarees, Designer Jodhpurs Wear, Lehenga Sarees, Panetar Sarees, Handwork Saris, Partywear Sarees, Printed Sarees, Anarkali Salwar Kameez, Bandhani Salwar Kameez, Bridal Jewelry, Bridal Lehenga, Designer Lehengas, Designer Salwar Suits......
